You look tired,Simon.
你看起来很累, Simon.
Didn't you sleep well last night?
你昨晚没睡好吗?
I had a very strange dream.
我做了个奇怪的梦.
Yeah?
是吗?
I went to Scotland to play golf.
我去苏格兰打高尔夫球.
That's not so strange.
那不奇怪呢.
But I played an amazing game.
但是我玩了一场神奇的比赛.
After the first seventeen holes,
在最初的17个洞之后,
my score was seventeen.
我的得分是17杆.
Seventeen?
17杆?
Seventeen.
17杆.
That means you hit seventeen holes-in-one.
那意味着你打了17个一杆进洞(holes-in-one)
One after another.
一个接着一个.
I hit that ball.
我击中球.
It flew through the air,landed,
它飞过空气, 落地,
and rolled into the waiting cup.
然后滚进下一个洞.
That's a great dream.
那真是一个很棒的梦.
I could do no wrong.
我怎么打都不会出错.
Until the eighteenth hole.
直到第18个洞.
What happened?
发生了什么?
It started fine.
开始挺好.
I drove onto the green.
我(把球)打到了球穴区(the green).
I was about three feet away from golfing history..
我距离创造历史只有3英尺(feet)
the lowest score ever.
史上最低分数(杆数).
Simon.What happened next?
Simon. 然后发生了什么?
Ninety-four putts.
94杆(putts).
That's no dream. That a nightmare.
那不是梦. 那是噩梦.